melrosejewelers.com 2010-05-24

# Melrose Jewelers USA Privacy Notice - Rolex Watches For Sale at Wholesale Prices, Used Mens & Lady Rolex Watches, Preowned Rolex President, Presidential & Rolex Datejust Watches

## Melrose Jewelers Privacy Policy

Last Updated: July 10, 2009

Thank you for visiting Melrose Jewelers. Here at Melrose Jewelers we want you to know that the privacy of your information is extremely important to us. As our customer, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information you share with us. The information in this Privacy Policy includes details on the following:

  * Information collected
  * Use of this information
  * Your choices
  * Information security
  * Potential modifications to this privacy policy

For further disclosure on the information provided on our site and the rules governing its use, please see our Terms and Conditions. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you may call us toll free at **888-574-1250** or email us at **inquiries@melrosejewelers.com**.

### Information Collected

Melrose Jewelers collects a variety of data from its customers and site users. We are the sole owner of this information, and will never share, sell, or rent this information to others in any way that is not fully disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

When you make a purchase from Melrose Jewelers you are submitting personal information to us and giving us your consent on the collection, use, and disclosure of this information as set forth in our Privacy Policy. This information may be stored and used for processing in any country that Melrose Jewelers or its partners maintain or use facilities, and by using our website you consent to the transfer of this information.

While browsing the Melrose Jewelers website it is not necessary to reveal personal information about yourself. We may, however, collect certain non-personal information from visitors to our site that cannot and will not be used to identify specific individuals. Information about visitors to our website that may be collected may include such information as IP address, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, referring and exit pages, software platforms, date and time of visit, click analysis, page views, demographic information, and other information that may be used to analyze patterns or trends, prevent fraud or abuse, optimize our product offerings or promotional efforts, understand your preferences or interests,  customize your shopping experience, or otherwise improve our website and customer service.

In some circumstances, Melrose Jewelers may also collect information via cookies or other collection devices and monitoring services to enhance your browsing and shopping experience. These cookies or collection devices may be used to measure the usability of our website, track visitors, track and measure the effectiveness of our marketing programs, learn more about how our customers and visitors use our site, or deliver better service to our customers and visitors. The information collected may include total unique visitors, pages viewed, time spent on pages or on the site in general, or other non-personal information used to improve the functionality of our website, our products, and our service.

If you decide to purchase a product or register an account on our site, we request personal information from you, and we may store the information you provide us—written or oral—via our website, e-mail, phone, fax, or other means. This personal information may be used to identify you and may include, but is not limited to, your credit card information (including name on the card, card issuer, expiration date, and CVV), your name, home address, billing address, shipping or other physical address, phone number, email address, gender, occupation, birth date, marital status, anniversary, other contact information, or additional information about your interests. The information you provide to us may be aggregated over time.  Additionally, we may combine this information with other publicly available information collected either by us directly or via our partners or other third-parties.

### Use of This Information

The information about you that we collect may be used for a variety of reasons, including the following:

  * Offering better or customized services or products
  * Improving our customer service, marketing, or promotional efforts
  * Identifying customer preferences and better understanding our customers’ interests and behaviors
  * Better understanding customer demographics
  * Responding to inquires and other requests
  * Facilitating purchases and providing requested services
  * Confirming, shipping, and tracking orders
  * Preventing fraud or detecting abuses of our services
  * Contacting users of our website—either by phone, email, mail, or other methods—regarding products or services that may be of interest to them

In some situations, we may have to share your information with trusted third-party service providers or other partners. This may be required to perform certain services on your behalf, including credit checks and verifications, credit card and other payment processing, shipping, data storage, website hosting, emailing, marketing, mailing, and other services related to managing visitor and customer accounts and running an e-commerce website. Please note that these service providers only receive the information deemed necessary for them to perform their specific service or function and are not authorized to use this information for any other purposes.

We are also authorized and may use your personal information for the purpose of preventing or thwarting crime, reducing the risk of fraud, and investigating or taking action against any illegal activities or suspected fraud. We reserve the right to use your information to ensure the safety of Melrose Jewelers personnel or other workers otherwise associated with the company. We also may use your information, if deemed necessary, to comply with applicable governmental laws, rules, regulations, or legal processes. Additionally, we may use your information to enforce any agreement we have with you, our customers, or visitors to our site. Finally, we may use your personal information to create anonymous records of your data for internal analysis. In the event of the sale of Melrose Jewelers or company assets, a merger, an acquisition, insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, personal information may be transferred as one of the assets of Melrose Jewelers.

### Your Choices

Melrose Jewelers gives you several choices in regards to the management of your information. If your personally identifiable information that Melrose Jewelers has collected changes, or you would like access to this data, Melrose Jewelers will gladly disclose this information to you or change, correct, or delete it, as allowed by law. To access or edit this information please contact us by either phone or email. If you prefer that we not share any of your personal information with third-parties—even if this results in less efficient service to you or our inability to provide a service or complete a sale to you—please contact us and we will satisfy your request. If you would like to opt out of our mailing list you may do so through our website by logging into the My Account section, or by contacting us directly. Please note that opting out of our mailing list or requesting that we not share any of your personal information with third-parties will not affect our communications with you, either by phone, email, or other method, regarding your orders place with us, nor does it affect the use of non-personally identifiable information.

### Information Security

At Melrose Jewelers and on our website, the security of any and all customer information—especially sensitive personal information—is extremely important to us and we are committed to taking precautions to protect it from unauthorized access or use both online and offline. For online transactions, Melrose Jewelers use a VeriSign 128-bit Secure Socket Layer—the strongest encryption available on the web—to guarantee your transaction is safe and secure.  Similarly, any data that may be stored offline is kept on secure servers with restricted access. No physical records or copies of personal customer information are stored, and any faxes or printouts with personal customer information are shredded and securely disposed of after their immediate use as may be necessary.

### Potential Modifications to This Privacy Policy

Melrose Jewelers reserves the right to modify or change this Privacy Policy, or any other practices pertaining to the usage or collection of information through our site, at any time without notice. If any modifications are made to our collection or use of information collected through our site, these changes will be reflected in a revised Privacy Policy, and this updated Privacy Policy will take effect when it is posted. This Privacy Policy is the most current version, and the date of its latest revision is listed at the top of the page. We encourage you to read and gain familiarity with this Privacy Policy. The use of Melrose Jeweler’s website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
